// This module contains NFL football trivia questions and answers.
const quizQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Which NFL team won the Super Bowl in the 2020 season?",
    options: [
      "Kansas City Chiefs",
      "San Francisco 49ers",
      "Tampa Bay Buccaneers",
      "New England Patriots",
    ],
    answer: "Kansas City Chiefs",
  },
  {
    question: "Who holds the record for most career touchdown passes?",
    options: ["Peyton Manning", "Brett Favre", "Tom Brady", "Dan Marino"],
    answer: "Tom Brady",
  },
  {
    question: "Which NFL team is known as 'America's Team'?",
    options: [
      "New York Giants",
      "Dallas Cowboys",
      "New England Patriots",
      "Las Vegas Raiders",
    ],
    answer: "Dallas Cowboys",
  },
  {
    question: "Who won the NFL MVP for the 2021 season?",
    options: ["Patrick Mahomes", "Aaron Rodgers", "Derrick Henry", "Tom Brady"],
    answer: "Aaron Rodgers",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team did the Philadelphia Eagles defeat in Super Bowl LII?",
    options: [
      "New England Patriots",
      "Pittsburgh Steelers",
      "Seattle Seahawks",
      "Atlanta Falcons",
    ],
    answer: "New England Patriots",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the trophy awarded to the Super Bowl champions?",
    options: [
      "Vince Lombardi Trophy",
      "Stanley Cup",
      "Larry O'Brien Trophy",
      "Commissioner's Trophy",
    ],
    answer: "Vince Lombardi Trophy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player set the record for most rushing yards in a single season?",
    options: [
      "Emmitt Smith",
      "Barry Sanders",
      "Eric Dickerson",
      "Adrian Peterson",
    ],
    answer: "Eric Dickerson",
  },
  {
    question: "Along with the New England Patriots, which NFL team has the most Super Bowl wins?",
    options: [
      "San Francisco 49ers",
      "Pittsburgh Steelers",
      "Dallas Cowboys",
      "Denver Broncos",
    ],
    answer: "Pittsburgh Steelers",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the first player in NFL history to rush for 2,000 yards in a season?",
    options: ["O.J. Simpson", "Jim Brown", "Walter Payton", "Barry Sanders"],
    answer: "O.J. Simpson",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What team did Joe Montana play for after leaving the San Francisco 49ers?",
    options: [
      "Kansas City Chiefs",
      "Denver Broncos",
      "Miami Dolphins",
      "Minnesota Vikings",
    ],
    answer: "Kansas City Chiefs",
  },
];

export default quizQuestions;
